So even though I scrap all the data, many of these links were like completely wrong or redirected to other pages or not safe to browse.
So for example, this one is sold on huge diamonds. This is like dangerous side. This is not related to it.
This is basically blocked. There's internal server arrow.
There is for some reason like Korean and I just remove it and I just mark each other's URL.
There are more than 1,200 rows and I had to like remove and fix other's URL because by default it's looking for QQuery and some of the search engines are using other syntaxes.
So for example, search test.
So what I can do now is just to remove all of the search engines that they mark remove and replace them syntax for the engine that has another link on the right.
So if you update the current ones and remove that one and remove those that they mark remove.
And then in the meantime, I will just update my file.
So this is with the scripts, I will remove all the scripts after but first I will run a new agent.
So I will open a new agent here so I can open the files here and I haven't a history because I moved my files but it's not a great deal because we still run a new agent on each feature.
So and first I will just ask for a ask what are top then search engines right now.
So as I am going to ask, you just try to confirm, so you do create like a MD file.
First, you do search right, I want you to implement top time search engines in my main and as you remember it was in the background.
So I can open it here and this is like the my top in my main search engine, like once by once got to go right country.
I can plus control that so it will just go to a plan agent and it will implement and now you run a new agent now again.
I show that actually some of the euros were like wrong.
I will implement AI search engines as well because then you think I will use awesome handbook.
So to open all of these links I will use extract on the main, I will open some of them because they cannot automatically ask them but I will show actually how we can use it.
This is the axe and I will just close it because it will duplicate.
So this is the first we see that we can send some coordinates but obviously if you ask something, it will directly search here.
And this is the sigma AI so we can go it here.
Can use this others is euro.
This is consensus.
Okay this one actually has a query where we can ask.
So I can use it and let me try again.
This is compiled or is test.
So it will open a new chat with unique ID.
So this way we can distinguish.
So this is test and this is another one.
This is the Gemini and we have a cosmo here we can just ask it.
So basically what I am going to do, I will use some of these others.
Although this is a demyq cannot use it.
I will explain the ones in the API key and I will just try to ask but look at this.
Okay we see it just has like a not fixed euro.
Unfortunately the only one is the consensus.
Nonetheless we can create an AI with adding this my manual stuff.
So it up you move some of the search engines and now replace it.
You see the changes right now here and now I will run a new agent.
W is my web browser.
I will ungroup it because I have it and I will place it directly here.
And so in the new agent I want you to add a search engine in my category and we can
mimic like this one AI search engine and provide these URLs.
So the first one will be and the search another one be sigma chat.
It is going to be touchability, gloat, so this is consensus up.
Now we will use maybe just the normal under zero here.
I will see we can create a further link function line that we will paste in the panel but
you have to find that part of the website and obviously write a script for that.
The fellow AI Gemini, my AI being an AI genspork AI, I have many of them perplexed AI and
find that AI.
So now I will just ask it and I will close all of this size.
I want to add some of the search engines.
So we just add a new category, presumably, so now we have to wait and I will just continue.
And we could probably add that we don't need an instructor because I just want to be like
a static neural address.
So what I am going to do, I can just alter it to a search dynamic here.
But maybe it will come up with some ideas so I will leave that as it is and see actually
the results.
Okay, as you can see it is now adding AI search engines.
Now it is creating a menu because I am using it, it is not this blank, but as you can see
it has been added like a new AI search engines, now we will populate the area, so we have
background.
I am glad that it is still keeping background.
All of the scripts will be removed by the end because I will clear them up, I just
temporary because like I said, I had to clear them on all of these and then I will just
ask to change it for our case, we see a tag manual, sometimes you have to do it especially
for some, go if I did, okay, I will just now use the query parameter, probably it will
not work but still in the sound case, I will just kind of use it so I will just go to
manage extension, I will not unpack it and now use Chrome search engine, sorry, and now
it is operated up, now when I mark it here, I will see multi-engine search, I will try
to use this platform and I will use search engine and we see that it is like AI search
engines, so here we can just try to file like a fiend, it adds some query but still it is
great and I don't think it will actually, it is like a possibility to add and for now you
need to add a query parameter to redirect to the place or try to put it in an AI search
model directly, if you can't put just manually redirect to the main AI search engine website,
okay so this case we can specify it and after that I will just run the last agent that
will create up all of the stuff, I will finish the extension but creating up the data and
the script files and then I will plug the Chrome web extension store, so as you can see
a mark of this remove the ones that they would actually remove, so I will open the new
agent, I will make here the file, as you can see I added remove after some addresses,
this remove those from search context menu and if the country doesn't have any addresses,
remove it entirely, another thing is to look for another address that is on the right side
of query address and I will just copy this for example from camera, I checked every URL
and look for a query, so you should replace word test if query because those search engines
use all the syntax and I will just press enter and after everything is done I will remove
all the scripts to maintain all the things, okay so as you can see it is processing, it has
some of the stuff and now we are just planning it next moves, great but what I mean is to remove
it from our main background, I am dated with new syntax ones and I removed those that
I mount remove and that case if it doesn't work we will just can return so it will just
go back but I think to just update it so I will just go to background JavaScript and see
how it looks like, let's actually stop it I think, let's go back here, date those changes
to background JavaScript, I think it will be more useful and it has been finished and
but there is one mistake, or an initial, it is AI data scientist, so we have AI search engines,
we have an North American or a united but there are some publicates, great but when I search
across search engines in context menu I see a duplicate of the address on a single instance of search
engine, so just make it, now we will go back again and just try to see how it looks actually
with the AI search engines, so it is under search, let's go directly because probably it
cannot just find easily, so if I type it again and go like complexity, it will go the
perplexity, it will just allow us to search and give the reminder of these things that
you can see here, we can try to change it directly to each one, so this by country and
this possibility to add this really great, and after that it should work, it will fail
and I see AI search, great, now we will just try to remove the duplicate engines and
we will place them, as you can see replacement has been completed, it will verify replacement
and clean up temporary files, so it is great to script for that, then just grab it and
next move, alright, so there are some changes, now if I go back to extension reload the
file, go to on the search, go to the country, I see now it works, so I have some of the
China yodao by doing, so if I open it up it will just look down, so yeah, this is how we
actually create a great extension, the last thing could be like a clear out, clear all
of and use it, takes the files and if only this is very files, so you can just think you
can combine, text, and other files, so how to separate it up, it will just also go to clean
probably to remove all of it, so it will just read over the code and then remove the ones
that are not specifically correct, we have now prefires again, and the last thing I want
to do by country and search engine should be at the very top of context menu, and if you
can use emoji in by country, context menu entry, use it at black or corresponding country,
so this will be like a small thing but I think people will love it, so that's some mapping
to create this function, okay, it will reorder that, and now it adds like emojis for that,
okay, probably to map something, our code is now very long, so if you are mapping it for
each country, so it was added, I will go to extension, I will upload, and now I will just search
for scientist search, I see this, and we see here in this in the countries of the code,
I search it at the top, and here we have like a Google being to other search engines,
so we did a lot, and now we will just add this extension with a new icon to the Chrome
webstation store.